Washingtoniana Slide Collection P026 P026
Test
- Series 5: Chamber of Commerce
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4836)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4837)
      Child sitting on ground with shoes and signs (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4838)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4839)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4840)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4841)
      Man carrying sign, "UFCW for a brighter future; March for freedom - register and vote" (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4842)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4843)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4844)
      Sign on top of trash heap, "America needs working people" (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4845)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4846)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4847)
      Two women carrying signs, "We want Jesse" and "Run Jesse Run" (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4848)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4849)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4850)
      Pete Seeger talking to male reporter (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4851)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4852)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4853)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4854)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4855)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4856)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4857)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4858)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4859)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4860)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4861)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4862)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4863)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4864)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4865)
      Crowd, signs on ground (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4866)
      Ruby Dee and Ossie Davis (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4867)
- Series 6: Christmas Slides
  - Christmas Slides (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Christmas (Ellipse), undated (Item 5000)
      Introductionary Slide for Holiday Slideshow
    - Christmas (Ellipse), undated (Item 5001)
      National Christmas Tree lighting with White House in background
    - Christmas, undated (Item 5002)
      Man giving the "ok" sign as a christmas tree is being loaded/unloaded from a railroad car
    - Christmas (White House), undated (Item 5003)
      National Christmas Tree arrives at the White House in a snow storm, tree from Vermont
    - Christmas (Ellipse), undated (Item 5004)
      National Christmas Tree being planted on the ellipse, Washington Monument in background
    - Christmas (Ellipse), undated (Item 5005)
      National Christmas Tree being planted on the ellipse, being held up by a crain with Washington Monument in background
    - Christmas (Ellipse), undated (Item 5006)
      Worker on scafolding near the top of the National Christmas Tree, Washington Monument in image
    - Christmas, undated (Item 5007)
      Artist, with pipe in mouth, shows design for tree topper for the National Christmas Tree
    - Christmas (Ellipse), undated (Item 5008)
      Tree Topper being placed on the top of the National Christmas Tree
    - Christmas (Ellipse), undated (Item 5009)
      National Christmas Tree covered in scafolding, White House in background
    - Christmas (Ellipse), undated (Item 5010)
      Natioanl Christmas Tree at night with Washington Monument in background
- Series 7: Olmstead
  - Olmstead (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - July 4th fireworks display on the Mall, undated (Item 5500)
    - Washington's Monumental Core, undated (Item 5501)
    - Grant Memorial, detail, undated (Item 5502)
    - Lincoln Memorial, undated (Item 5503)
    - Arlington Cemetery, undated (Item 5504)
    - US Sanitary Commission headquarters, undated (Item 5505)
    - Olmsted Portrait, Ca. 1896 (Item 5506)
    - Vaux portrait, undated (Item 5507)
    - Gallaudet Chapel, undated (Item 5508)
    - Plan of Gallaudet Campus, undated (Item 5509)
    - Olmsted Green, undated (Item 5510)
    - Academic Building and Green, undated (Item 5511)
    - President's House, undated (Item 5512)
    - Bicycle Club at Faculty Row, undated (Item 5513)
    - Faculty Row, undated (Item 5514)
    - Architectural detail of arch, undated (Item 5515)
    - Colorful gothic revival materials, undated (Item 5516)
    - Loggia, undated (Item 5517)
    - Detail of Walter Dome, US Capitol, undated (Item 5518)
    - Old and new Capitol grounds (before and after Olmsted), undated (Item 5519)
    - Olmsted portrait, Ca. 1868 (Item 5520)
  - Olmstead (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - East approach to Capitol, undated (Item 5521)
    - East façade, undated (Item 5522)
    - Olmsted plan for Capitol grounds, undated (Item 5523)
    - Capitol west terrace, undated (Item 5524)
    - West terrace, undated (Item 5525)
    - West Terrace, with urns, undated (Item 5526)
    - West stairs, undated (Item 5527)
    - West stairs, down into Mall, undated (Item 5528)
    - Detail of ironwork on stair rail, undated (Item 5529)
    - Sculpture relief on gate post, undated (Item 5530)
    - Wall arounf grounds, undated (Item 5531)
    - "Edge" of Capitol grounds, undated (Item 5532)
    - Result of "building around the square" from air, undated (Item 5533)
    - Approach to the Capitol from East, undated (Item 5534)
    - West grounds with ancient trees, undated (Item 5535)
    - Autumn tints on West grounds, undated (Item 5536)
    - West grounds parklike character, undated (Item 5537)
    - Walk in park, undated (Item 5538)
    - Couple relaxing, undated (Item 5539)
    - Historic print of steam train and horse trolley at west enterence, undated (Item 5540)
  - Olmstead (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Detail of spring house (grotto), undated (Item 5541)
    - East capitol plaza and car parking, undated (Item 5542)
    - Trees and parked cars, undated (Item 5543)
    - Lopped tree trunks, undated (Item 5544)
    - Tree surgery with heavy equipment, undated (Item 5545)
    - Tree surgery with chains, undated (Item 5546)
    - Formal photo of tourist group, undated (Item 5547)
    - Tourist group breaking up, undated (Item 5548)
    - Vendor's umbrellas at pond, undated (Item 5549)
    - West grounds, from above, undated (Item 5550)
    - Tree label, undated (Item 5551)
    - Patched walkway, undated (Item 5552)
    - Ellipse and White House grounds, undated (Item 5553)
    - Mall and pedestrain way, undated (Item 5554)
    - Great space of Mall with birds, undated (Item 5555)
    - Frederick Law Olmsted, Jr., 1930 (Item 5556)
    - Swept gravel walkway, undated (Item 5557)
    - Mall and crowds, undated (Item 5558)
    - Sun and shadows, undated (Item 5559)
    - Mother and Child on the Mall, undated (Item 5560)
  - Olmstead (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Children playing on Smithsonian dinosaur, undated (Item 5561)
    - Office party alfresco, undated (Item 5562)
    - Drawing of shelter belt; Olmsted's philosophy of trees and public health, undated (Item 5563)
    - Street Trees, New Jersey Avenue, NW, undated (Item 5564)
    - typical residential block North of Capitol, undated (Item 5565)
    - Ghinkos display and Victorian row houses, undated (Item 5566)
    - P St., East of Logan Circle, undated (Item 5567)
    - A Wide street in the L'Enfant plan, East Capitol Street, undated (Item 5568)
    - Rock Creek in Winter, S. of Military Road, undated (Item 5569)
    - Rocky stretch of Rock Creek, undated (Item 5570)
    - Hardwood forest in Rock Creek Park, undated (Item 5571)
    - Cyclist on closed highway in park, undated (Item 5572)
    - Historic Pierce Mill restored, undated (Item 5573)
    - Olmsted sketch of trolley stop shelter, undated (Item 5574)
    - Rock retaining walls in park, undated (Item 5575)
    - cycle club in Rock Creek Park, undated (Item 5576)
    - Cobble bridge (Glen Brown), undated (Item 5577)
    - Cobble bridge detail, undated (Item 5578)
    - Olmsted Sr. Portrait, ca. 1893 (Item 5579)
- Series 8: Truax Slideshows
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Arizone Avenue), undated (Item 6000)
      "Flood stage - B and O bridge over land, Arizona Ave" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6001)
      One man and two women sitting in rapids (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6002)
      Two men looking at water (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6003)
      Snow covered house and hillside, icy water (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6004)
      Bridge over open canal gates (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, near Great Falls), undated (Item 6005)
      Small boat in canal, two people walking in distance (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, near Widewater), undated (Item 6006)
      "Camp on C and O Canal near Wide Water"; empty canoe on shore (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Georgetown), undated (Item 6007)
      Bridge over canal and structures alongside (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Georgetown), undated (Item 6008)
      Boats in canal, mules on towpath (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Georgetown), undated (Item 6009)
      Boats under bridge (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6010)
      "Young child tethered to boat" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Chain Bridge), undated (Item 6011)
      Bridge over canal and two men on shore (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6012)
      Man, woman and child on wooden footbridge (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6013)
      Man sitting on top of boat next to dam (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Willard's Lock), undated (Item 6014)
      Boat "approaching Willard's Lock"; man and mules on towpath (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6015)
      Three boats, man sitting on top of first boat (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, near Chain Bridge), undated (Item 6016)
      Boat pulled by mules, white structure to side (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6017)
      Men on boat, two boys in swim trunks (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6018)
      Man on blanket next to tent (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (Key Mansion, Georgetown), Ca. 1900 (Item 6019)
      Key mansion, Potomac River (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (Key Mansion, Georgetown), Ca. 1910 (Item 6020)
      Key mansion and adjoining structures (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Seneca Lock), undated (Item 6021)
      People and mules on towpaths, boat and structure in distance (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Georgetown), undated (Item 6022)
      Boats with American flags (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6023)
      Two men holding gates open for approaching boat, Canal Towace(?) No. 32 (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6024)
      Man in canoe (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6025)
      Child tethered to boat (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6026)
      Boat towed by mules (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6027)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6028)
      Canal (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6029)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6030)
      Water flowing through gates, lockhouse (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6031)
      Boat in water, men walking on towpath (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6032)
      Boat in front of dam, structures in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6033)
      Structure made with part of a boat (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6034)
      Empty lock, lockhouse (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Willard's Lock), undated (Item 6035)
      Woman operating gate (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6036)
      Small dam next to a house (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6037)
      Bleachers? (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal, Willard's Lock), undated (Item 6038)
      Man in small boat, man operating lock (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6039)
      Man sitting on top of open flood gates (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6040)
      Four boats with rowers (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6041)
      Stone house, man in window (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6042)
      Woman on boat in lock, man on dock (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6043)
      Boys in canoe passing larger boat (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6044)
      Water flowing over dam, lockhouse (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #1 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6045)
      Stone house (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6046)
      "Washington: Then and Now" (Photographer: N/A)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6047)
      "A Presentation of" (Photographer: N/A)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6048)
      "Statues in the City" (Photographer: N/A)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6049)
      "For More Information…" (Photographer: N/A)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6050)
      "Made Possible in Part by…" (Photographer: N/A)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6051)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6052)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6053)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Shaffer's Lock), undated (Item 6054)
      "Shaffer's Lock"; water flowing through gates; structure to side (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6055)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6056)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6057)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6058)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6059)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6060)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6061)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6062)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6063)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6064)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6065)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6066)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6067)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6068)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6069)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6070)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6071)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6072)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6073)
      Boat in canal, two men walking on towpath (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6074)
      Water flowing over dam, men in boat (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6075)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6076)
      Lock with open gates (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6077)
      Water flowing through lock gates, man operating gates on top (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Seneca Lock), undated (Item 6078)
      "Seneca Lock, open"; People and mules on towpaths, boat and structure in distance (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6079)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6080)
      Two children tethered to boat (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6081)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6082)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Lock 16), undated (Item 6083)
      "Lock 16, 13.63 m."; Man sitting on top of boat, water flowing over dam (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6084)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, near Great Falls), undated (Item 6085)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal), undated (Item 6086)
      Man on top of boat, several boats in distance (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Willard's Lock), undated (Item 6087)
      "Willard's Lock (Lock #5) 5.2 m"; Man in small boat, man operating lock (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Willard's Lock), undated (Item 6088)
      "Lock #5 Willards"; Woman operating gate (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Willard's Lock), undated (Item 6089)
      "Approaching Willards Lock (Lock #5) 5m"; Boat towed by mules (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Chain Bridge), undated (Item 6090)
      "Chain Bridge"; Bridge over canal and two men on shore (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, near Chain Bridge), undated (Item 6091)
      Boat towed by mules, structure on shore (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Arizone Avenue), undated (Item 6092)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Georgetown), undated (Item 6093)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Georgetown), undated (Item 6094)
      "Canal boats at Georgetown" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Georgetown), Ca. 1900 (Item 6095)
      "Francis Scott Key House" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Georgetown), undated (Item 6096)
      Stone bridge over canal (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2 (C and O Canal, Georgetown), undated (Item 6097)
      Canal with structures on shore (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6098)
      "A Presentation of" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6099)
      "Made Possible in Part by…" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6100)
      "The Library for the Arts of the District of Columbia Public Library" (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6101)
      "The C and O Canal" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - C and O Canal Set #2, undated (Item 6102)
      "For More Information…" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Building, undated (Item 6103)
      Large red brick building, cars in parking lot (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Building, undated (Item 6104)
      Large red brick building, trolley car (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Canon, undated (Item 6105)
      Canon (replica?) outside stone building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Belasco Theatre (Madison Place, Lafayette Square), undated (Item 6106)
      Belasco Theatre building at night, snow on ground (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Winter Street Scene, undated (Item 6107)
      Snow covered street leading to Capitol, horse-drawn carriages, buildings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Building, undated (Item 6108)
      Four story building with turret (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Building, undated (Item 6109)
      Six story building with turrets (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1834 (Item 6110)
      "Pennsylvania Avenue, Washington, 1834"; Postcard view, colored drawing (Photographer: Unknown)
    - White House (White House), undated (Item 6111)
      The White House (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Bright Light (Potomac River?), undated (Item 6112)
      Bright light over buildings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Lansburgh's (8th Street NW at D Street NW), undated (Item 6113)
      Lansburgh and Brother department store and surrounding buildings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Mansion, undated (Item 6114)
      Sketch of mansion with horse-drawn carriage outside (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Ford's Theatre (Ford's Theatre, 511 10th Street Northwest), undated (Item 6115)
      Ford's Theatre, Yale Laundry (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Building, undated (Item 6116)
      Three story brick building on corner (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Building, undated (Item 6117)
      Three story red brick building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Harvey's Oyster House, undated (Item 6118)
      Harvey's Oyster House and surrounding buildings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Building, undated (Item 6119)
      Man with unicycle outside four story building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Redwood Tree House (National Mall), undated (Item 6120)
      Redwood Tree House (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Willard's Hotel (Pennsylvania Avenue), Ca. 1850 (Item 6121)